

Behnam Khoshsafar

SENIOR SOFTWARE DEVELOPER - JAVA

PROFILE

Nationality: Iranian
Birth Date: 09/06/1990

A passionate and hard-working developer with experience in designing and developing software in Java since 2014.

Participated in implementing different types of applications specializing in backend development. Skilled in Spring, JPA, and Object Oriented Design.

EDUCATION

Master of Science from Qom University in Information technology - E-commerce from September 2012 to February 2015.

Bachelor of Science from Kurdestan University in Information technology from September 2008 to September 2012.

LANGUAGES

English

Persian

CONTACT

Email: b.khoshsafar@gmail.com

Mobile: +98 937 375 1121

LinkedIn: Khoshsafar's profile

WORK EXPERIENCE

MyDigipay

Senior Java Developer

Mar 2019 - Present

- Working as a member of the Credit team.
- Responsible for designing and implementing the Installment module.
- Responsible for designing and implementing the Refund module.
- Responsible for designing and implementing the Report module.

Sava Arman Kish (Bitex)

Senior Java Developer

July 2018 - Mar 2019

- Worked as a member of the development team.
- Responsible for designing and implementing the Order module.
- Responsible for designing and implementing the Notification module.
- Responsible for designing and implementing the Report module.

Navaco (Maskan Bank)

Java Developer

Feb 2017 - July 2018

- Worked as a member of the Lending team.
- Designed and implemented lending overnight calculation.
- Designed and implemented the Letter of Credit subsystem

Hamgam Corporate Group

Java Developer

April 2014 - Jan 2017

- Worked as a member of the development team.
- Responsible for designing and implementing the Sale module.
- Responsible for designing and implementing the Inventory module.



Behnam Khoshsafar

SENIOR SOFTWARE DEVELOPER - JAVA

PROGRAMMING SKILLS

Java 11	Spring
Groovy	Spring Boot
Design Patterns	Spring MVC
Microservices	Spring Batch
Test Driven Development	Spring Security
Concurrent Programming	Spring Cloud Config
RESTful Web Services	Spring Cloud Netflix
JUnit / Mockito / WireMock	Spring Cloud Gateway
Oracle	Spring Data / JPA
MySQL	Spring WebFlux
MongoDB	Reactive Programming
Redis	Eureka / Ribbon / Hystrix / Zuul Netflix
Hibernate	Maven / Gradle
Docker and Docker Compose	Git / Subversion
CI / CD	UML / Agile and RUP Methodologies
RabbitMQ	Lending System Developer
Exchange Developing	CORE Banking Systems